

Contacts

Phone: 669-622-625

E-mail: oskar.drygalski@gmail.com

Tech skills

Known

- MS Office
- Visual Studio Code knowledge
- Language skills
- Customer service
- JIRA

In progress

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- C#
- PHP
- Database Management

Soft skills

- Creative
- Teamwork
- Communication
- Adaptability

Oskar Drygalski

I am a 2nd year computer science student and a member of the InnoGames team for over 2 years. While living in Great Britain I worked and trained English Language I was involved in the production of luxury mattresses there. Two years ago I decided to return to Poland. Additionally, in the previous year I completed a bartending course and started learning Spanish.

I spend most of my free time on inccreasing my skills by learning about the aspects of a front-end developer, as it is my dream job in the future. My hobbies include windsurfing, IT curiosities as well as football. Since September this year, I am also a volunteer at a shelter for homeless animals.

Projects

- 1. elektrykow.netlify
- 2. retrogranie.netlify
- 3. przejscia.netlify
- 4. szubienica-gra.netlify
- 5. philosophyblog.netlify

Employment history

Volunteer In-game Operator and Senior in-game Operator at InnoGames

February 2019 - up to now

- Customer service
- Handling complaints against game operators
- Helping new team members with transition to the role of game operator

Bartender at Ulica Elektryków

June 2020 - November 2021

- Customer service
- Preparing drinks
- Keeping bar areas clean and neat

CO-Community manager at InnoGames

June 2021 - up to now

- Customer service
- Team management
- Managing scripts and technical matters

Quality Assurance at InnoGames

November 2021 - February 2022

- Handling of upcoming bugs / proposals
- Testing existing events configuration tickets
- Create weekly reports

Education

Computer Science, Banking college

September 2020 - June 2023

Front-end Developer, Udemy

January 2021 - in progress